BUSINESS LICENSE
PROPERTY REGISTRATION CERTIFICATE
REGISTERED FOR HAN JEONG-U
REGISTRATION INFORMATION
THE LATE HAN JEONG-U
10 YEARS AGO
BOXING
THE 94TH NATIONAL CHAMPIONSHIPS
BOXING ARENA
REGISTRATION CERTIFICATE
HOSPITAL NOW! SU-JIN
THE 94TH NATIONAL CHAMPIONSHIPS
BOXING ARENA
1ST PLACE WINNER KIM SU-CHEOL
THE 94TH KOREAN NATIONAL CHAMPIONSHIPS
DONGSEONG UNIVERSITY HOSPITAL
MEDICAL DIAGNOSIS
PATIENT: KIM SU-CHEOL
CHRONIC TRAUMATIC ENCEPHALOPATHY
PUNCH DRUNK SYNDROME: CTE FOR BOXERS
BRAIN CELL DAMAGE FROM REPEATED BLOWS
HAN JEONG-U, TRAUMA CLEANER
SANG-GU'S OLDER BROTHER!
MAKE SURE THEY MEET!
Subtitle translation by: Jean S Kim